(Space Rice Cake)
(Last night, after the hectic business is over...)
(They made a new kind of rice cake, and it's called...)
(Sticky rice cake)
(The chewy charm sparked the Earth Arcaders' inspiration.)
(Under Mimi's leadership, they launched a new menu item.)
(The chewy sticky rice cake sheet makes it charming.)
(Potato cream tteoksagna)
(The dessert team launched a new dish as well.)
(A sticky rice cake sheet is added to black sesame ice cream.)
(Good Night Black Sesame Torong Ice Cream)
(Amazed)
(They successfully developed new sticky rice cake menu items.)
For today, we're limiting it...
- to just 5 servings.
- So the total is 10 servings.
- Yes.
- When they ask how many are left...
Mimi, I think this dish will sell well.
(Staggering)
(While staggering, she flips the open sign.)
(Current time: 12pm)
Okay. Let's go.
Let's do this!
- Let's do this!
(The lunch rush begins.)
Eun Ji, shall we taste the dongchimi?
Okay.
We made it three days ago.
But I think we should check the taste.
- And then we'll...
- I think we should taste it.
Right.
Should we just taste the broth?
- Is it okay?
- Yes, it's good.
- It just needs to be kept cold.
- We've got this.
Honesty, humility.
- Is it supposed to taste like this?
- Yes.
Okay.
(The yuzu dongchimi that has turned perfectly sweet and sour...)
We should put it in the fridge now.
(will be chilled with a layer of slushy ice before being served.)
My heart is beating like crazy.
Same here.
We have corns in here. What are in those two containers?
(In the main kitchen, the chefs are walking on thin ice.)
(Clattering)
(With tension in the air, all we can hear is the metal clattering.)
(Space Rice Cake)
(Unaware of the chefs' jitters, customers start rushing in.)
- Hello.
Oh, my. Please walk a little slower.
Please walk slowly from there.
Please walk slowly.
- I should put them here...
- Instead of walking fast.
They're coming.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Hello. How many in your party?
A party of 3 here, and another party of 3 here, right?
I'll show this party to your table. Please come this way.
Would you like a table outside?
- Yes, please.
- That sounds great.
Please take a look at the menu first.
- Let's bring them some water.
- Okay.
We have customers at two outdoor tables.
- Got it.
- They're looking at the menu.
- Potato cream tteoksagna...
- What is...
- Cream butter tteok.
- The serving size might be small.
- It's hard to say those names.
- That one is...
Let's just order original...
- Original tteokbokki.
- Order whatever you want.
Our menu items have unique names, don't they?
- It's difficult to read, isn't it?
- Yes.
Unfortunately, we only have five servings...
of potato cream tteoksagna for today.
I highly recommend that you try this dish.
As for Goguryeo Ramyeon...
Do you know the opposite of "ssaguryeo" as in "cheap?"
(What are you talking about?)
Someone said it was "goguryeo."
Hey, guys, a customer asked for ramyeon yesterday.
"Oh, they serve ramyeon too."
Many customers said things like that.
(The ramyeon they're talking about...)
(was originally whipped up as a staff meal.)
(And it made it onto the menu on their first business day.)
(Goguryeo Ramyeon)
(The opposite of "cheap" is "goguryeo.")
Mimi, come to think of it, no one ordered ramyeon today.
Ramyeon is not the best choice for today's weather.
Right. That's true.
- There's a demand...
- Right.
- for ramyeon.
- People are curious about it.
Let's add it to the menu again.
(So the ramyeon made an unintentional comeback!)
Will that be okay with you?
The problem with Goguryeo Ramyeon is...
What did I put in?
(Since it was improvised, there's no official recipe for it.)
Please discuss it together and let us know.
- Original tteokbokki...
- I want...
- and Goguryeo Ramyeon...
- Yes.
Ji Woo and Ji Hwan, do you want ramyeon?
We'll have tteokbokki, ramyeon,
and cream butter tteok. What about you, Ji Woo?
- May I take your order?
- Honesty, humility.
- Ahk.
- Yes.
(The creator of Goguryeo Ramyeon)
Hello.
Please have some yuzu dongchimi while waiting. We made it.
I brought some small bowls...
- so you can share it.
- Thank you.
Ms. An Yu Jin.
Yes, I'm An Yu Jin.
(Yu Jin's appearance made the girls shy.)
Here's yuzu dongchimi.
- Share it together.
- Okay.
I need the olive oil spray. Coming through.
Mimi, you have a lot more to do today.
- I can do it!
- Beef loin.
When you think it's impossible, it becomes impossible.
When you think it's possible, it becomes possible.
Yes, that's the spirit!
Darn!
(She must be feeling the pressure with the new dishes on her mind.)
Mimi, go.
Mimi.
- We got our first order.
- Okay.
(Right then, the first order is in.)
One small original tteokbokki,
one Goguryeo Ramyeon,
one cream butter tteok,
one potato cream tteoksagna,
one pomegranate slushy, and one soda.
One Goguryeo Ramyeon?
Yes. I think we'll get more orders for Goguryeo Ramyeon.
Goguryeo Ramyeon?
They're very curious about the ramyeon.
(The sheer pressure made her hunch over.)
Potato cream tteoksagna?
Goguryeo Ramyeon.
(And she repeats the name of the menu item.)
Potato cream tteoksagna will be ready shortly.
(She regained her composure after that shout.)
I wrote only "tteoksagna."
Really? I wrote "potato cream."
- Should I write "tteoksagna?"
- I'll fix what I wrote.
No, I'll write "potato cream."
(To prevent confusion, they agreed to nickname it "potato cream.")
We got an order.
One small original tteokbokki,
one Goguryeo Ramyeon,
one pomegranate slushy,
and one potato cream tteoksagna.
- Is it for a different table?
- Yes, it's for Table Five.
(Order Status: two small original tteokbokki,)
(two potato cream tteoksagna,)
(two Goguryeo Ramyeon)
The original tteokbokki will be served first.
Stay calm.
I'll try to remember the recipe for Goguryeo Ramyeon.
We took it off the menu yesterday, but we brought it back today.
This is the second ordeal the universe has thrown at me.
I completely forgot about Goguryeo Ramyeon.
(The first ordeal was making rice cakes.)
(The second ordeal is making Goguryeo Ramyeon.)
(And there's another one who's facing an ordeal.)
I think... The potato cream sauce, mozzarella, sticky rice cake,
and the ragu sauce. Okay.
Stay calm. It's okay.
(Place white baekseolgi first.)
(Add the potato cream sauce on it.)
(Plenty of mozzarella)
The rice cakes seem to be in perfect condition.
(Cover it with a sticky rice cake sheet.)
You did a great job making the ragu sauce.
- Me?
- Yes.
Young Ji, you made such great ragu sauce.
(Adding the ragu sauce simmered to perfection by Young Ji)
(Finishing it off with a sprinkle of grated cheese)
Young Ji, I just have to put them in the oven.
Parsley is... Excuse me.
(Getting in each other's way)
(Their clumsiness level goes up.)
Here goes...
- pollack roe cream lasagna.
- Okay.
(It's potato cream tteoksagna.)
(It entered the pre-heated oven.)
(Order Status)
(Tteoksagna, in progress)
All right. Now, let's think.
(Young Ji starts making Goguryeo Ramyeon.)
(Step 1: Adding one ladle of broth)
I'm starting with 500ml.
Now... Goguryeo Ramyeon.
(Step 2: Getting flustered)
Eun Ji, the ragu sauce turned out so well.
The ragu sauce is wonderful,
- and there's no rush.
- Okay.
No rush at all.
The original tteokbokki will be ready first.
Should we take it off the menu?
No, that's okay. I'm starting to remember the recipe.
I'm Lee Young Ji. It's okay. I can do this.
I'm the king of the kitchen.
Since Goguryeo Ramyeon is luxurious, I don't add dried vegetable flakes.
(She uses fresh vegetables for toppings to make it luxurious.)
You can do it.
(But she adds the sauce as required.)
- Who are you?
- I am Lee Young Ji.
It's so hard to be me.
Try living as Lee Young Ji in your next life.
It must be hard. I can't live like you do.
What do you mean by that?
- It means you're so cool.
- What does it mean?
The tteokbokki is ready for now.
- Is it ready? The fried food...
- It's almost ready.
- Just give me two minutes.
- Okay.
(She starts making fried sides at the right time.)
(Since it's a rice cake restaurant, she adds chopped garaetteok.)
Oh, gosh. What was the recipe?
It was something like this in my memory.
(She adds her blurry memory too.)
(Since it's ramyeon, she adds noodles too.)
(The other members' worries are added too.)
Here are the broken pieces.
No broken pieces in Goguryeo Ramyeon. Here.
(Goguryeo Ramyeon Rule: No broken noodles allowed)
(Interim evaluation)
How does it taste?
It's incredibly tasty.
(She gives herself a rave review.)
You can take the raw shrimps here.
(The umami crafted by corporate researchers)
It's fried to perfection.
(The hot fried sides are ready.)
It's really hot.
(Jumping like a frog)
It's okay. You're doing great.
- Don't forget the sesame.
- Don't worry. I won't forget it.
Do you think I'll forget it? I will never forget the sesame.
This is all because I came up with that stupid pun.
- One small tteokbokki is ready.
- Okay.
- Another one is ready too.
- Please put it here.
(Order Status: Tteoksagna, in progress)
(Original tteokbokki, ready)
(Goguryeo Ramyeon is currently the same as regular ramyeon.)
I should lower the heat now.
(She works on the Goguryeo Ramyeon again.)
- Can I add the seafood now?
- Yes.
Oh, right. I forgot the meat. Darn it.
(She gained the beef loin in the freezer.)
(Swift)
(Adding a generous fistful of meat)
(The pot is fully packed now.)
- Hold on a second.
- But the broth... Is that okay?
Doesn't it have too little broth?
(Approaching)
(Laughing quietly)
Don't you worry.
(Young Ji gets timid.)
- Shall I bring you some water?
- No, I have broth right here.
(And the Goguryeo Ramyeon boils down.)
(Order Status: Tteoksagna, in progress)
(Goguryeo Ramyeon, stir-fried noodles)
- We got another order for ramyeon.
- Thank you.
(Thank you.)
- Because of Goguryeo Ramyeon...
- We're all flustered.
What if the customers complain about the food?
The first order of Goguryeo Ramyeon is a bit...
(The service team is worried about the difficult new menu item.)
It's difficult.
(While everyone is worried, the first Goguryeo Ramyeon is done.)
(The final check)
- How does it taste, Young Ji?
- It's good.
- It's really good.
- It must be. I'm sure of it.
(It tastes good, but it looks a bit...)
- It does taste good, but...
- Right.
- Is this Goguryeo Ramyeon?
- Yes.
How about we make Goguryeo Ramyeon on the house just for today?
Just so they can try it.
(It's on the house today.)
- It's done, right?
- I just have to add parsley.
Tteoksagna is ready.
(Sprinkling parsley on top)
Ta-da. How does it look?
- It looks good.
- It turned out well, right?
(Order Status: Tteoksagna, ready)
(Goguryeo Stir-fried Ramyeon is on the house.)
Do you know the opposite of "ssaguryeo" as in "cheap?"
(It's "goguryeo.")
Could you please... Thank you so much.
(Feeling bad, she serves the food by herself.)
This is our first time serving this dish.
- Please enjoy...
- It smells good.
It will taste "luxurious."
I hope you like it. Please enjoy.
(Yu Jin is serving the tteoksagna.)
- Thank you so much.
- What is this?
It's potato cream tteoksagna.
(Three siblings' table: Everything except for ramyeon has been served.)
Here's the potato cream tteoksagna. It's really hot.
Please be careful. I'll put it in the center.
(Family's table: All orders are out, except for cream butter tteok.)
- It looks good.
- What's this?
(They try Goguryeo Stir-fried Ramyeon first.)
This can't be real.
(Despite all the worries, the customers like the ramyeon.)
This cheese is really amazing.
(They're loving the tteoksagna too.)
- Mimi, - Yes?
I'll make it perfectly this time.
- You should try it, okay?
- Okay.
You were just a little flustered. That's all.
Ever since we opened, every day feels like an eternity.
I feel like I first made this ramyeon...
when Goguryeo was founded.
It feels like last year.
Hello. How many in your party?
- Four.
- Your table is ready inside.
(While Young Ji is time-traveling back to the Goguryeo era,)
(the descendants of Goguryeo are storming in.)
- Hello. How many in your party?
- Hello.
- Four.
- Four?
We only have five servings of potato cream tteoksagna for today.
And currently,
two servings have been served.
So we only have three servings left.
We started to serve potato cream tteoksagna today.
We started to serve it today.
Is it like lasagna?
Yes, it's lasagna made with rice cakes,
which are baekseolgi and sticky rice cake.
- And we only have...
- I'm sorry to interrupt.
- We only have one tteoksagna left.
- They have ice cream too.
- You have one serving left?
- Yes.
We only had five servings for today.
- We got a new order.
- Okay.
- No way.
- For Table Two,
- one small original tteokbokki, - Yes.
- one small mala tteokbokki, - Yes.
one pollack roe and clam pasta, two cream butter tteok,
two coffee slushies, two pomegranate slushies,
one small Broccolino Basiliano,
two potato cream tteoksagna, and one black sesame ice cream.
- We got a new order.
- Okay.
One potato cream tteoksagna,
one small mala tteokbokki,
one black sesame ice cream, one pomegranate slushy, and one soda.
(Order Status: original tteokbokki, mala tteokbokki,)
(pollack roe and clam pasta, Broccolino Basiliano, tteoksagna)
Potato cream tteoksagna is sold out for today.
- Is it already sold out?
- Yes.
(Only 5 servings were available.)
(Tteoksagna is sold out.)
(She layers rice cake and sauce one after another.)
(She adds a sticky rice cake sheet and gives it a gentle pat.)
(Then, she spreads a massive layer of ragu sauce.)
- Go, tteoksagna.
- Let's go.
(Adding a nutty, savory flavor with cheese)
(They enter the oven side by side.)
(While tteoksagna is flooded with orders,)
(one dish is nowhere to be seen on the order sheets.)
(Goguryeo Ramyeon is missing.)
I'm upset because everyone is ignoring Goguryeo Ramyeon.
No one is ignoring it, Young Ji.
Some people out there don't know what Goguryeo tastes like.
- You can let them know today.
- That's...
(Chuckling)
Mimi, you sound like you're on autopilot right now.
(She got caught.)
I'm adding the noodles.
(Young Ji starts making the second Goguryeo Ramyeon.)
(This time, the noodles stay firm, and the broth is kept just right.)
Nice. I have a good feeling about this.
Chef.
This ramyeon deserves to be served at a fine-dining restaurant.
(As the dish turned out quite well, she starts dreaming big.)
- Goguryeo Ramyeon is ready.
- Okay.
(Ancestors' taste, Version 2, is ready.)
Here's your Goguryeo Ramyeon.
This one is also very hot.
Please enjoy.
(She moves a generous portion to her plate to taste it.)
It's really good.
Tteokbokki is my specialty.
(She's finally back in her element.)
Goguryeo Ramyeon is like my side job.
(She seems way more steady while cooking on the stove.)
I can grab exactly five pieces of fishcake by pure intuition.
(Her arrogance is first-rate.)
The rice cakes are in perfect condition.
(Her rice cake coiling skill is also first-rate.)
Yu Jin, can you cook beef loin... Never mind.
- Cooking beef loin?
- Yes.
- Sure. I'll do it.
- Thank you.
(She starts cooking beef loin for the mala tteokbokki.)
Goguryeo Ramyeon, the sad, miserable ramyeon.
(She just can't let go of it.)
It's okay. If you're tired, that means everything is going well.
Yes, Chef.
In that case, everything is going really well.
- Yu Jin, the beef loin...
- Yes?
Should I cook this at a specific heat level?
No, I have no idea. Just cook it as you want.
Yes, ma'am.
Young Ji, you're doing really great right now.
Thank you. You're amazing.
(They compliment each other.)
You're like Usain Bolt.
(To our dear Misain Bolt...)
(Pollack roe and clam pasta is just a warm-up.)
- Mimi, How many servings...
- Yes?
of fried sides can you make?
- I need 2 servings...
- Sure. I can make 2 servings.
(Making fried sides for tteokbokki is the bare minimum for her.)
- That's just enough.
- These are looking amazing.
Original tteokbokki is ready.
Broccolino Basiliano is ready.
- Mala tteokbokki is ready too.
- Okay.
(And mala tteokbokki as well)
- Potato cream tteoksagna...
- Please change the pot...
- is ready.
- I already served it.
- All 3 of them are ready.
- And there are 2 of these.
(Three servings of tteoksagna are ready too.)
(Order Status)
(All done)
Table 5 ordered 2 servings. So, 2 for Table 5...
and 2 for Table 2...
And 1 for Table 4.
Two for Table Two.
I'll serve the food for Tables 2 and 4.
- Let's make desserts after that.
- Okay.
You ordered the potato cream tteoksagna, right?
(Seal's duties: Waiting tables)
We don't have the POS system.
- Pomegranate...
- Are you serious?
One pomegranate slushy, three dollars.
Your total comes to 24 dollars.
Would you mind if I double-check?
(It's their 3rd business day, and counting up is still difficult.)
Original tteokbokki... Thank you. I hope to see you again.
Thank you.
- Welcome. A table for two?
- Yes, please.
Please give me a moment.
(Seal's duties: Processing payments, Welcoming the customers)
Please take a seat. I'll clean up the table.
(Seal's duties: Welcoming more customers)
It's not easy for us to run a restaurant.
- It's not an easy job.
- Right. I'm sorry.
- Let me help you.
- That's okay, ma'am.
Thank you. Hello.
I'm sorry, but let me check if we have a table available.
Could you please tell me your name?
It's Lim Se Ron.
- Lim...
- Se with an "e."
Se. All right. We'll let you know right away.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- There's a waiting list.
- Okay.
(Pushing)
Goodness.
- I'll do it!
- Thank you.
- Goodness.
- I'll get you some water.
- Thank you! Please wait a moment.
I don't think I'll be able to go out until I finish this.
(It's time for Eun Ji's new dessert.)
(Finely ground soybean powder)
(Injeolmi syrup drizzled with a dramatic snap)
(She gets out sleeping Torong.)
(A cozy sticky rice cake blanket)
(See you in dreamland, Torong!)
This is the first time serving this.
It's a summer blanket, and I folded it in half.
That's so cute.
- Like a mother.
- You've got this.
Let's go!
(She delivers Torong No. 1 with cheers.)
(Sleeping Torong's appearance brings out exclamations.)
Cut off a small piece of the rice cake on top...
and eat it with the black sesame ice cream...
to fully enjoy the flavor.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Enjoy.
(Mission accomplished with a perfect explanation.)
(My blanket!)
(While Torong was willingly making the ultimate sacrifice...)
That was nice.
Let's go.
Hi...
- Let's go!
- There!
(Strange things are happening in the kitchen.)
It's a crazy day for you today.
(Mimi lost it from being overworked.)
- Yes.
- And...
is the potato cream tteoksagna sold out?
That's right.
Then...
What's that one over there?
That's the tteoksagna.
There are only five of those.
Since it's a new menu item we launched today,
we limited it to just five servings.
Should I check with the kitchen to see if we can serve them?
All right.
The five tteoksagnas we promised have been served,
but could we get more orders? What do you think?
- You can get more orders.
- I can?
Then I'll forget about the limited servings today...
and keep getting orders.
Okay.
(Servings secured)
There's good news.
We can take orders for the tteoksagnas.
Thank you.
(She happily announces that more servings are available.)
Kim Mi Hyun will be preparing it. Kim Mimi.
(Laughing)
- She's sweating inside.
- Goodness.
- We have an order.
- Okay.
(And...)
Two small original tteokbokkis,
two pollack roe and clam pastas, and six coffee slushies.
One pollack roe and clam pasta,
one small Broccolino Basiliano,
one pomegranate slushy, one coffee slushy,
one black sesame ice cream, and one tteoksagna.
Good luck. You've got this.
- We've got this.
- One more order.
One small original tteokbokki,
one potato cream tteoksagna,
one pollack roe and clam pasta, one black sesame ice cream,
- and one soda.
- Okay.
(Mimi's list of things to struggle with)
I'll make two at once.
- I can do it.
- You can do it.
(Mass cooking begins.)
Why isn't it coming off?
You're the best.
Nice. It's...
These are two servings.
(It's less like stir-frying and more like lifting weights.)
(Two servings of pollack roe and clam pasta done in no time)
(Making the tteoksagna tower next)
(Finishing the final layer of cheese with care)
Should I try frying it?
- Sure, give it a try.
- How do I do it?
Do I put it in now?
- Hold on.
- Okay.
Good. Let's go.
(Temperature check complete, let's go!)
(The sound passes the test.)
I don't know when to remove it.
(Mimi said the key to frying is...)
One minute and thirty seconds.
(time and temperature.)
(A stopwatch firmly in hand...)
(and tense shoulders from the nerves)
(This is the moment!)
(It's as if she's frying them with her expressions.)
Young Ji.
(Crispy seafood fritters are ready.)
- Producer.
- Yes?
You're done with this, right?
- Could you help us with this?
- Yes. I'm done with that.
The frying pan.
(The pay is 1 mala tteokbokki per hour.)
You got this, middle-aged man!
(Exclaiming)
Soon to be a senior...
- I'm not a senior yet.
- It's just around the corner!
You got this.
You'll hit old age soon too.
The time has come...
(Another moment of teamwork arrives at the register.)
for everyone to join forces.
Please keep a close eye on things by my side.
Two butter tteoks.
That's 6 dollars plus 6 dollars, which is 18 dollars.
- Twelve dollars.
Twelve dollars plus...
One black sesame. That's seven dollars.
I think the total is 206.5 dollars.
Sorry?
It's 206.5 dollars.
(Was the tteokbokki covered in gold?)
Is 206.5 dollars correct?
Someone watching me.
(Silence)
Yes, hold on!
(Rushing)
Hold on.
The Register Fairy!
(The Register Fairy arrives.)
- I'm in trouble.
- Hello.
I'll go inside, Yu Jin.
One small original tteokbokki.
It's 80.9 dollars. Am I right?
- That almost went bad.
- Is it 80.9 dollars?
- How did you get 200 dollars?
I don't know.
It's 80.9 dollars?
- That almost went bad.
- It's not?
No?
Should I check again?
I'm sorry.
- This is crazy.
- One small original tteokbokki.
- Get us a POS system, Yeong Seok!
- That's nine dollars.
One small mala tteokbokki. That's 11 dollars.
We don't have a POS system.
We don't have a POS system. Thank you.
(Complaining about the working conditions to everyone)
- It's correct.
- It's 99.4 dollars!
This also...
Take care! Thank you!
(The fairy has finally finished checking out!)
(The customers leave.)
(For some reason, the fairy studies the recipe.)
Yu Jin is reading the recipe.
(Feeling concerned)
(She uses the spare time to set up the dessert for Eun Ji.)
(Neatly drizzling the injeolmi syrup)
(She checks the recipe to see if she made any mistakes.)
I think you should start preparing the ice cream.
- I set up the dishes.
- Okay.
Would you like to sit here if this spot works for you?
Please help me.
I'm so grateful.
(Busy Eun Ji finally gets to work on dessert, thanks to Yu Jin.)
How nice of her.
(She covers Torong, being careful not to wake him up.)
Here's your dessert.
- Thank you.
That's cute.
You can cut the rice cake...
and eat it with the ice cream to enjoy it even more.
- Thank you.
- I'll bring you a knife.
This is so cute.
They're good.
It's chewy.
One hundred eighty-three. One hundred eighty-two.
In three minutes.
(She also adds semolina.)
Lasagna for table three...
(While the tteokbokki expert kept busy making fritters...)
One for table three and one for table five.
We've waited a while for the tteok, right?
(Checking the time)
What time is it?
Let me check if you're missing anything.
- Okay.
There are many dishes that haven't come yet, right?
I'm sorry.
All right.
Table five is wondering when they'll get their order.
One small original tteokbokki? It'll be out in one minute.
(Unlike her answer, her facial muscles look quite flustered.)
(The three tteokbokki brothers, forgotten in the thrill of frying)
(The seafood fritters she worked so hard on for so long...)
(are generously piled on top of the tteokbokki.)
- One small original tteokbokki!
- Okay.
The second small original tteokbokki is ready.
Thank you. There's one more small original tteokbokki.
- They're here.
- Here are two servings.
- Okay.
- It's hot.
- Here's your tteokbokki.
- Okay.
- Please don't touch the pan.
- Thank you.
I'll bring you some tongs and scissors right away.
- Okay.
- Your small plates as well.
(Just as the forgotten dishes finally found their places...)
(Kim Mimi hurriedly opens the oven.)
Do you know what I forgot?
I remembered it halfway through.
(She forgot the Parmigiano cheese.)
(It balances the flavor with umami and saltiness and makes it brown.)
No one noticed it.
- This is for table two.
- Basil.
(Things are starting to fall apart a little.)
Thirty minutes?
We have 30 minutes left.
(30 minutes until last order)
The last order... But I don't believe in those things.
I think it's a myth.
Last orders are a myth in the restaurant business.
Excuse me!
- Yes, can I help you with anything?
- Yes.
What is this used for?
(It's a mic.)
(Sir!)
- That's...
- A mic.
- That's a mic.
You're not supposed to eat that.
(After sharing a good laugh)
I'll get them some knives.
(She puts on her shoes and returns to the kitchen.)
Enjoy your meal.
(Meanwhile, Yu Jin was serving.)
(Her shoes are gone.)
(Eun Ji put on her shoes and went.)
(She became a Cinderella...)
Eun Ji.
(She first gets Eun Ji's tiny shoes.)
Eun Ji!
Should we switch shoes just this once?
- Okay.
- Yours don't fit me.
You're wearing mine.
I'm sorry.
(She became Jean Valjean.)
Earlier...
Do you know what the man at the outdoor table said?
He picked up the mic with his chopsticks...
and asked if he had to eat that as well.
(Giggling)
So I told him not to.
The one on the table...
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
- You can stop now.
- But...
(Another old man sharing happiness by doing the dishes)
- The small dishes are hot!
- Thank you so much!
- Please be careful.
- Middle-aged man.
- Thank you so much.
Middle-aged man, middle-aged man.
- Today...
- You've earned it.
Na Yeong Seok, the young man!
(Congratulations! Na Yeong Seok has gotten younger!)
- You've earned it.
- Young man, young man.
Twenty-four years old!
Thank you. "Youth Over Flowers," thank you.
Young man, young man.
(Meanwhile, some real young women arrive at the entrance.)
- Hello. Table for 2?
- There are 4 of us.
Four?
Four of you are here.
(All the indoor and outdoor tables are full.)
- Take a look at the menu for a bit.
- Okay.
Here's your potato cream tteoksagna.
(The mother and son table:)
(Everything is served except for...)
(Good Night Black Sesame Torong Ice Cream.)
(Exclaiming)
- Is that a potato?
- It's baekseolgi.
Here's your pollack roe and clam pasta.
(The local elders table)
Here.
- Here's your...
- Yes.
potato cream tteoksagna.
- I guess that's gamjatang.
- We should have tried that.
- It's really hot. Be careful.
- It has potatoes.
This is also tteok.
I think it was made with tteok.
I like tteoksagna the most.
(I like tteoksagna the most!)
(Meanwhile, Eun Ji...)
How is it going there?
How is it going with your orders?
(She wisely tries to take their orders in advance.)
- Torong Ice Cream.
- Torong Ice Cream. Two servings?
- Two servings.
- Please wait a little.
- Okay.
We have an order.
(She shares it with the kitchen right away.)
(Last order: small original tteokbokki,)
(small mala tteokbokki, tteoksagna, pollack roe and clam pasta)
They're waiting for a table, so there's no rush.
I took their orders in advance. I'll clean up a table right now.
Okay.
Take your time, Mimi. I'll...
do everything including the fritters.
(Exclaiming)
Go, go.
It feels like paradise to prepare one pollack roe dish...
after continuously making two servings.
It feels like paradise?
(Thanks to her reliable sister, she can start cooking with ease.)
It feels like paradise to make only one serving now?
Yes.
One serving...
- It gets done in no time?
- gets done in no time.
It gets done in no time. It's scary how that's possible.
It also doesn't take me more than five minutes to do this.
Getting used to something is such a scary thing.
Today, I can talk,
I'm not getting sweaty on my upper lip.
- Something's...
- You're even making the fritters.
I'm even making the fritters. Something's...
Why am I used to this?
Why am I feeling fine?
Something's not right.
Something's not right, Mimi.
Right.
Making all the tteokbokki...
Yesterday was hectic.
That's right.
(Mimi's frying pan effortlessly cooks the clams too.)
(For some reason, the oven is the only thing not working.)
(5 minutes ago...)
(Orders taken in advance from the waiting guests)
(One potato cream!)
(The order definitely came in.)
(She even replied.)
(Kim Mimi turned her back on the oven.)
We're basically experts now.
(Experts? She left out part of the order.)
Table three came first...
Where's table three?
The one at the end?
(Leaning forward)
One, two, okay.
- I'll do it. Please keep an eye.
- Should I do it?
(She comes back without noticing the tteoksagna.)
Where's the salt?
- Five, four...
- I'll go then.
- Okay.
- three, two, one.
(She dances, completely unaware of what's going on.)
The clam pasta is ready.
Okay.
(Kim Mimi is done celebrating her own achievement.)
(The tteoksagna was forgotten like that.)
Here's your pollack roe and clam pasta.
I'll come back with some tongs and scissors.
I'll get you some small plates.
(The head chef gets bored with the familiar routine.)
(Blank eyes)
(The lively days of her life pass by.)
Right now. Goodness.
Get it out.
(The slightly overcooked but nicely done fritters...)
(are placed on top of the tteokbokki to finish the dish.)
- The mala tteokbokki is going out.
- It's coming.
- Okay.
- It's for table five.
I don't normally serve dishes.
(The waiting table)
(Last order)
(Tteoksagna left)
(The last dish of the last order)
(Only Mimi is unaware.)
That's table five. The one outside. You can serve that now.
It's been solved.
The left one or the right one?
Table five. All the tables are on the left.
- I covered it with a blanket.
- That's right.
Right here.
Hello.
Are you enjoying your meal?
My sister really likes you.
Really? Why are you not a fan?
I...
- Mimi.
- I guess I'm not your first choice.
Why did you do that?
I served them two tteokbokki dishes,
and they didn't tell me they were my fans.
I have them all.
That's not polite.
This is done, right?
(The service team organizes the order slips.)
(Among the completed orders...)
(Creepy as it may be, there's one main dish left.)
Tteoksagna?
Did she not prepare that?
- Hello.
- Say hello.
(The tteoksagna expert is still unaware.)
(She's having a peaceful time with a baby customer.)
He's so cute.
Mimi.
Leave that and come here quickly.
Just you.
(It sounds like a serious call.)
There's one tteoksagna that needs to be served,
but it hasn't been made yet.
One tteoksagna.
Why didn't you make it?
Did I forget to say it?
You're not being scolded. Just prepare one now.
- Okay.
There's one tteoksagna left on the order,
but it's going to take around ten minutes.
Please wait a little longer.
- It's really tasty, though.
- Thank you.
(She asks the customers for their understanding.)
They're still eating. You don't need to rush.
It's for the table that just started to eat, right?
Yes. The table with four ladies. Just do what you normally do.
(She first preheats the oven...)
(and calmly layers the tteoksagna.)
(But...)
I'll just reduce them a little.
Let's eat this together.
(She forgot the sticky rice cake layer.)
(This time, she doesn't forget...)
(to place the sticky rice cake layer.)
(She also doesn't forget to add the Parmigiano cheese.)
(She doesn't forget to put it in the oven.)
(10 minutes later)
Thank you for coming. Take care.
- Bye.
Bye.
Thank you. Take care.
(The customers start leaving with a smile from the Register Fairy.)
- Bye.
- Thank you.
(The customers start leaving with a smile from the Register Fairy.)
(The last customers are waiting for the tteoksagna.)
(It'll be out in a minute!)
I'll serve it myself.
Your dish is here.
Be careful. It's hot.
Don't touch it.
There's baekseolgi at the bottom,
then there's the sauce and sticky rice,
so it will stretch out like this.
Enjoy the dish. You can use the knife.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
(Enjoy your meal.)
- Is it good?
- Yes.
- It's like pasta.
- That's right.
(Fortunately, the customers are enjoying the dish.)
When's the last order?
- I think we can wrap it up now.
- Okay.
(Open for business)
(Closed for business)
(They finally wrap up after all the ups and downs.)
(Now it's time for a little break.)
(It's time to check today's sales.)
Let me just say one thing.
I'm burned out.
(3 days in, and she's already out of motivation.)
- You...
- She has to go home.
- I'm going home.
- She's going home.
- How much is it?
- This might cure the burnout.
- Why?
- It's 489.3 dollars.
- Only during the daytime?
- Yes.
- How...
- How did the sales go up?
- I think the ice cream...
- The ice cream.
- Yes. It's seven dollars.
- How did the sales go up so much?
- I think it's because of ice cream.
Goodness. We really...
The upward trend in sales...
- It went up. We worked hard.
- How is it?
- On the first day...
- Tell us the total amount.
We made 93.3 dollars in sales...
- at Yeong Seok's table.
- Yes.
We made 296.8 dollars...
- on the next day.
- Yes.
Then we made 775.9 dollars.
It's on an upward trajectory.
(Yes!)
(As sales go up, so does their mood.)
Do we only have reservations for dinner?
- Yes.
- One team?
We've been talking about doing a rice cake omakase, so...
Who talked about that?
- The head chef.
- When...
- Did I talk about that?
- When did she say that?
- I didn't mention that!
- The head chef said,
"We could do something like a rice cake omakase!"
No. Seriously.
(Fine dining)
(A formal meal...)
(or an upscale restaurant that serves such meals)
You know, seriously...
We can go with a rice cake omakase.
(To make sure we don't take the head chef's words lightly...)
(I'm really sorry.)
(Even though we're a fine-dining restaurant...)
(You know,)
(we wanted to go with a fine-dining style...)
(To show our appreciation for the servers' professionalism,)
(tonight's dinner will be fine dining!)
Please keep your mouths shut!
I have a disastrous mouth...
I have a disastrous and terrifying mouth,
but why does it seem like only the negative things I say...
come true?
- Why is that?
- "We'll earn 10 million dollars."
Such words don't come true.
But we have 16 people coming.
They're people who helped us.
They're from the National Livestock Cooperatives Federation.
They said they wanted to have a team dinner.
So people we're grateful to...
are coming to enjoy a rice cake omakase?
(The reason we're grateful is...)
(Day 1, when sales were particularly slow)
(National Livestock Cooperatives Federation's H Mart)
(We'll give you a discount on short loin!)
(Goheung's generous hospitality came to the hungry.)
(So, since we're doing fine dining anyway,)
(we decided to be the grateful magpie...)
(Correction, the grateful Rice Cake.)
- Then let's do rice cake omakase.
- Yes.
- What's the first course?
- But...
Isn't serving everything the best?
- We should plan it.
- Are you serving Goguryeo Ramyeon?
- Not Goguryeo Ramyeon.
- No?
- Rice cake omakase...
- I think,
- for an appetizer, - We need dongchimi.
we need the cream brulee rice cake.
- Should we serve dongchimi?
- Yes, serve dongchimi.
- Serve dongchimi first.
- Yes.
- Serve cream butter tteok.
- Okay.
I'm worried about...
whether to serve clam pasta first...
- or original tteokbokki first.
- No, the original.
The original tteokbokki.
Cream butter tteok...
- and original next.
- Pollack roe after cream...
The original tteokbokki.
I think the clam pasta is a good idea.
After the clam pasta, let's serve mala.
Clam pasta, mala, and basil. It's a good idea.
- Clam pasta, mala, and basil.
- Basil.
After mala, it's tteoksagna.
- Ice cream?
- Serve ice cream.
Ice cream.
What if they want more? What if they're still hungry?
- That's unlikely.
- Right.
They'll be stuffed.
(The final order of rice cake omakase)
(Yuzu dongchimi, cream butter tteok, original tteokbokki, clam pasta,)
(mala tteokbokki, Broccolino Basiliano, tteoksagna, ice cream)
- What time are they coming?
- At 6:30pm.
- What time is it right now?
- It's 5:30pm.
- Not bad.
- Let's talk in the kitchen.
- Sure.
- And decide the plates.
We could serve pollack roe...
- and clam pasta here.
- Right.
Or the cloud rice cake.
- The cloud rice cake?
- Yes.
The cream butter tteok is...
the beginning of fine dining. So I know it's a hassle,
but let's serve cream butter tteok in the tteokramisu bowl.
Serve it in the tteokramisu chestnut bowl.
- Serve dongchimi in dongchimi bowl.
- Serve it here.
- Can I add apple mint to it?
- You got it.
- Let's do that.
- Hold on. That's so funny.
Is there something we can do...
- with the cream butter tteok?
- Right.
- What should we do?
- Write an S with whipped cream.
- What?
- Or write universe. Be creative.
- Right.
- I'll use my fingers...
to make a cloud with the whipped cream.
I know what you mean.
- I know what you mean.
- You mean this?
- I'll do that.
- Okay.
It's going to be busy for the service team.
The servers are important for fine dining.
Can you put clam pasta here...
and write R, O, C, K with caramel syrup?
Rock? You mean rock?
(Sticking to the name)
- But...
- Get me the caramel syrup.
- We could use a toothpick instead.
- Right.
(Finding it funny)
- Why are you suddenly excited?
- This is fun.
- You like fine dining.
- I've never been to one.
(She's seen it even though she's never been to one.)
I can't do it.
- That's not bad.
- Yu Jin, you try it.
(Trying an advanced decoration again)
(Fill the gijeongtteok with cream.)
(Sprinkle minced chestnut powder.)
(Doing something with the cream)
How about this?
- But...
- Isn't this right?
This is the first course of our rice cake omakase.
- But that's...
- It's cream...
It's cream butter tteok.
(The cream butter tteok with a mysterious beard)
- Is this what you had on your mind?
- I was thinking...
- Just wait.
- Use this.
Try it.
- Like this.
- Yes.
- Yes, something like that.
- You got it.
There.
- Yes.
- This is it.
- Something like that.
- Down here.
I wanted to try that, but I couldn't.
There was something else I wanted to try.
Let me try. Let me pursue my dream.
Go ahead.
I'll cut this in half.
(Add cream in between.)
(More cream on top)
If we grind it,
it'll look nice.
Hey.
That's crazy.
- That's so nice.
- Hey, that looks nice.
Here is the cream gijeongtteok.
- "Gijeongtteok."
- That's so tall.
(Looking pretty fine)
(Meanwhile, the kitchen team)
(Scribbling something)
(In agony)
- Mi Hyun.
- Yes?
About pollack roe and clam pasta,
how do you serve it?
I remember 1 bar of rice cake, 2 fish cakes, and 2 sausages.
- Is that right?
- First...
- Here is the bowl.
- Okay.
- Place the rice cake here.
- Place a bar of rice cake.
Fritters go here.
(Sharing the ideas for presentation on a small board)
- Thank you.
- What do you think?
Thank you.
Sausages, two basils...
You know what?
I think...
rice cake omakase is harder.
Did I really say I wanted to do rice cake omakase?
It was me? Are you sure it wasn't someone else?
(Yes, it was you.)
Because I talk a lot.
You know how this feels?
We can do this in Seoul.
We're ready to open in Seoul.
(Ms. Terrifying Mouth, please be quiet.)
(Young Ji rolls the rice cake after that.)
- Young Ji, I'm frying cod too.
- Okay.
(The service team prepares the desserts.)
Every day is a new world.
Isn't that surprising and thankful?
- Yes. We should be grateful.
- Gosh.
- I'm grateful once again.
- What time is it?
It's 6:25pm?
- Five minutes left, everyone.
- Yes, chef.
Smile.
(Starting business with a smile)
(Current time: 6:30pm)
We're now open.
(Open for business)
(Getting ready to greet the customers)
(Silence falls over the kitchen as the time draws near.)
Let's say it together.
- Honesty.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
The spoons...
You're a true leader.
Instead of a true leader,
can I be the king of kitchen?
You're the king of kitchen.
Thank you.
(The king of kitchen is nervous.)
Our purchase is finally paying off.
Seriously.
(A row of 16 people surrounds the restaurant.)
(The biggest number of customers appears.)
(16 people from National Livestock Cooperatives Federation in Goheung)
(They draw near mercilessly.)
I think they're here. I'll be outside.
Good luck.
- Good luck.
- Bye.
(A large group of customers is entering.)
Hello.
Welcome to Space Rice Cake's...
fine dining, rice cake omakase.
- Hello.
- It looks cool.
Please follow me.
- Hello. Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
- Hello.
Please proceed inside.
(Crowded)
Nice. This is perfect.
What was his name again?
(The wall of gallery on one side)
I know. I've seen him.
- I sent it.
- It's supposed to be like this.
- Maybe he helped them with cooking.
- That might be it.
- But his pose is...
- I love it.
(The Mona Lisa of Goheung)
- Nice to meet you. Hello.
- Hello.
Welcome to Space Rice Cake's...
fine dining, rice cake omakase.
You're from the National Livestock...
- Cooperatives Federation?
- Yes.
Chef Lee Young Ji was very happy to hear...
that people from the National Livestock Cooperatives Federation...
were coming.
(Smiling)
(Laughing)
Things look good outside.
You have the whole place to yourselves for dinner tonight.
You may relax and enjoy it.
I'll briefly explain the dishes to you.
They'll be served in order.
Before that, we'll start with a welcome drink on the house.
We have pomegranate slushy and coffee slushy.
Raise your hand if you want pomegranate slushy.
(16 zesty pomegranate slushies)
All of you?
Please give me a moment.
- Thank you.
Take your time. I'll give them slushies...
- on the house.
- Thank you.
(Preparing slushies first)
(She has to repeat it 16 times.)
(All set by herself)
I'd appreciate it if you could receive it.
- Here are your slushies.
- Thank you.
- You're beautiful.
(Shy)
We're one short.
- You're one short?
- Two.
My apologies.
- I can't count.
- Take this...
(We'll serve it quickly.)
(Yu Jin prepares dongchimi.)
I'll add apple mint.
I bought the tweezer tongs for this moment.
(Finally making use of the tweezers)
(Finishing up with apple mint)
I'm plating with my best...
as if I'm feeding apple mint in their mouths...
one by one.
I finished it up with apple mint.
Here is the first meal...
of rice cake omakase.
This is yuzu dongchimi,
but today, I'd like to call it...
the Cheot Mannam.
(Cheot Mannam, expressing the first meeting with Livestock Coop)
I can never forget my first meeting...
with the team manager in the store.
As I said earlier,
he gave us a big discount on Korean beef.
How much discount did you give them?
(At a loss for words)
The store manager is here too.
You're making him feel uncomfortable.
The name of this dish is the Jeomjangnim.
Allow me to serve you yuzu dongchimi.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
I love you, store manager.
(Thank you.)
(While everyone tries Jeomjangnim)
- This is an important moment.
- We have to work on that.
Yes, it's an important moment.
I'll put the sand below.
(Sprinkle the minced chestnuts like sand.)
(Next up is the chocolate cream.)
(Piping the cream between the grilled rice cakes)
(Finished in a perfect clam shape)
It's a special, precious clam crafted just for our dear customers.
We tried to describe the ocean through this dish.
My, it's pretty.
Honestly, I think it's a good-quality dessert.
- I amazed myself.
- It's really great.
- I'll push the cart. Go ahead.
- Okay.
(They leave with their second dish to share this sense of awe.)
- I'll do original tteokbokki first.
- Okay.
(The kitchen team starts making the main dishes.)
(A large 16-serving wok appears.)
- Okay.
- Got it.
I'm just following my instinct.
(Scooping up a big spoonful of sauce)
(She makes rich and flavorful broth.)
In goes the rice cake.
(Here goes the 175-centimeter-long garaetteok.)
(The king of the kitchen looks serious.)
(Next up is mala tteokbokki.)
(Scoop up a generous spoonful of chili bean sauce.)
(And bring the broth to a full boil first.)
It will take quite a long time.
(She's cooking 32 servings all at once.)
(I can do this)
(Please say it to me)
(She's extremely nervous right now.)
(Serving the second dish)
- Could you take the bowls, please?
- Sure.
(Feeling bad)
- Please pass them down. I'm sorry.
- Okay.
We put extra love and care into this...
Oh, that's some heavy cologne you're wearing.
(That's none of your business.)
- Thank you.
- Is it good?
She can take this.
(One cream tteok is left unclaimed.)
We have an extra one left here.
- You have an extra one left?
- Yes.
Why is that?
- You can have it. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
It's Chocolate Cream Clam Gijeongtteok.
That's right.
(Course 2: Choco Cream Gijeongtteok)
(Korean style butter tteok inspired by clams in Goheung)
This is a masterpiece, inspired by the sea of Goheung,
right outside the window.
Please enjoy. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- We'll enjoy this.
- This is fun.
- It's hilarious, Eun Ji.
(I'm so excited.)
(The customers take a bite.)
(While the customers are enjoying the second dish...)
(The tteokbokki has been simmered to perfection.)
(Placing the pots quickly)
(When all 16 pots are prepared...)
You... Show me how to do it first.
- I'll show you.
- Okay.
(Portioning out individual servings)
Please let us know first.
(One of each kind of fried food)
Shall I sprinkle sesame?
Sounds good, Chef.
The head chef will add the final touch.
Nice.
It looks luxurious.
(Meanwhile, Chef Mimi is...)
(making pollack roe and clam pasta.)
(The biggest batch she has ever made)
- Gosh, it's so heavy.
- You've got this.
This is my...
- Your signature plating?
- This is my signature plating.
It's my signature plating.
Oh, boy. I'm scared.
Yu Jin.
Shall I carry one of them?
(Waddling with a hunched back)
Here's Chef Lee Young Ji's original tteokbokki.
Thank you.
- My, it looks delicious.
- Thank you.
It's original tteokbokki developed by our head chef Lee Young Ji.
Yes, that's right.
This original tteokbokki captures...
Chef Lee's dopamine-boosting charm.
Enjoy your meal. Thank you.
- Thank you.
What are we doing?
(A sudden wave of humiliation takes over.)
(Something is off.)
They shouldn't discriminate with food like this.
Take a look at this. Look at the sesame.
(Sesame?)
- What's wrong?
- Look at this.
(The unfair sesame distribution controversy spreads like wildfire.)
- Sesame.
- He got so much sesame.
(Feeling wronged)
Can you pass me the sesame and the garnish?
We have one left to finish.
(Earlier on...)
(Pouring out)
Oh, no. I added too much sesame.
(It was just a slip of the hand while sprinkling the sesame.)
That's special treatment. It's not fair.
(We hope the misunderstanding is cleared up now.)
They're going wild.
- How did they react?
- As soon as we passed by...
(She vividly reenacts the customers' reactions.)
They were amazed by the presentation of the food.
I think it makes them feel truly special.
What's the second main dish?
- It's pollack roe and clam pasta.
- I see. Thank you.
(The pollack roe and clam pasta is almost ready.)
My wrists...
hurt.
- Be careful. It's ready, Eun Ji.
- Okay.
Yes, Chef Mimi.
Chef Mimi, if you have time,
- add the final touch, please.
- Okay.
(Chef Mimi's final touch)
Please portion it out first.
- With my hands?
- Portion it out.
- Oh, portion it out?
- She's touching the plates.
(It's because it's so hectic in here.)
(Embarrassed)
(Now, she stays focused as she plates the food.)
It's done, Chef.
(Adding a pop of color with red chilis)
I'll garnish with rosemary.
(Adding a special touch with rosemary)
My goodness. Look at that.
(It looks just like a fine-dining dish.)
- It looks so fresh.
- My goodness.
The rosemary makes it look perfect.
Eun Ji, we need to...
- We need to take these away.
- I'll do it.
(For a moment, they forgot about the empty bowls.)
Everyone got... Why do we have one left here?
(There's one serving of tteokbokki left on their serving cart.)
I think we keep miscounting the plates.
- We made one more dish earlier.
- Oh, I see.
Since we miscounted, we have one serving of tteokbokki left.
Why don't you taste it, Chef Lee?
(She heads to the dining area to see if anyone didn't get the food.)
(Actually, the customers...)
(finished with their food long ago...)
(and even cleared the table.)
- It was so tasty.
- Thank you.
(Rushing)
They finished eating and are waiting for the next dish.
- I just wanted to let you know.
- Let's hurry.
(As they heard about the customers waiting for the next dish,)
(they start moving more quickly.)
(Everyone is so busy.)
Coming through.
I'm sorry.
- This is the last one.
- We'll be back shortly.
(Eun Ji heads out to serve the food right away.)
(Watching carefully)
We're missing two, Eun Ji.
I'll go check.
(It feels like an ominous beginning.)
(Is one missing?)
(The counting mistakes...)
(they've been making since the beginning...)
(caught up to them as karma.)
(Mimi, who has no idea of what's happening out there...)
Try this.
See if it's seasoned right.
(No, Mimi.)
(The shadowy hands behind the window took the leftover food.)
Is it too salty?
Mimi, are you sure you prepared 16 plates?
- I'm not sure.
- We need two more servings.
(But the real problem is...)
We have no jeolpyeon left.
I can make more food, but we have no jeolpyeon left.
What do we do?
Yu Jin.
- Yes?
- Can I start now?
(We're still missing two!)
(What do we do?)
(Eun Ji is left alone to face the 16 customers.)
- The mala tteokbokki is ready.
- Okay. We can prepare this...
just as we did earlier.
I wonder how Mimi can handle the missing two servings.
(You don't have to cry)
(Eun Ji is playing her hidden card.)
(Eun Ji's tear-jerking struggle)
(Sweet and mellow)
(I will make you smile)
Thank you.
(A round of satisfied applause)
Slowly.
(They start serving the food with two servings missing.)
Here you go.
(And Eun Ji...)
Actually, I forgot to tell you something.
For the team manager and the store manager,
our chef will be serving your food directly.
If that's all right with you?
(That would be even better.)
Is that okay?
Then the two of you will have to...
just watch the others eat while waiting.
- Would that be okay with you?
- Yes.
- Thank you. I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Can we start eating now?
Please go ahead.
(The rest of the customers start eating.)
- Please go ahead and dig in.
- Let's dig in.
- Please enjoy.
- That was funny.
(With smooth problem-solving, Eun Ji put out the biggest fire.)
(Meanwhile, Young Ji is starting a fire.)
- Are you catching the wok...
- While you're working busily...
- on fire on purpose?
- I'll serve it as it is.
- Sorry?
- It's not intentional, right?
(Chuckling)
She was asked if she was catching the wok on fire on purpose.
(Never try this at home. Call 911 to report a fire.)
- Okay.
- Beef loin? Hold on.
I'm doing it right now.
(Mimi is making the missing servings of pollack roe and clam pasta.)
- I made it delicious.
- Good.
(They're portioning out the mala tteokbokki.)
Give it to us.
(The middle-aged man is doing the dishes.)
They must be really eager to eat this.
- Mimi, after that...
- Can you help me with this?
Chef Mimi will serve it directly.
(Chef Mimi heads out to serve the food directly.)
- Hello.
Who didn't get the pollack roe and clam pasta?
- Here.
- Me.
- I'm really sorry. I honestly...
- It's okay.
I'm still new to this.
Thank you.
For the store manager and the team manager,
I made it a bit spicy.
Please enjoy.
I love you.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Give it to us.
Counting, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, and 16.
Let's plate them.
(They're almost done now.)
- Then, right now...
- Why do we not have enough shrimps?
Deep-fried shrimp...
(Only one shrimp remains.)
They're done eating. Can we serve the mala now?
Some are without shrimps.
- We don't have plates.
- Which plates?
The small pots.
It's not ready yet.
Can the shrimps be ready in a minute?
Then I'll wait for it.
Not yet.
- When do you need them?
- Now.
How many minutes do you think?
I'm so sorry,
- but about 1 minute 30 seconds.
- About 1 minute 30 seconds?
- Let's wait, then.
- We'll wait.
(The final order of rice cake omakase)
(Mala: No shrimps, Basil and tteoksagna: In progress)
(She prepares tteoksagna...)
(while waiting for the oil to heat up.)
(The beads of sweat on her forehead shows how hard she's worked.)
(Young Ji deep-fries shrimps instead of tired Mimi.)
(Nervous for no reason)
- Where are deep-fried shrimps?
- Where is the lid?
(Looks like they're being deep-fried well this time)
(The shrimps are finally ready.)
- Not yet.
- It might be here.
- It's hot.
- I'll use tongs.
- Yu Jin, here you go.
- Thank you.
(With much effort, they cooked enough shrimps.)
Here you go.
(The fifth dish sets off.)
Allow me to explain the name of the next dish.
It's Bhut Jolokia Don't Eat It Tteokbokki.
- What did you say?
- Come again?
- We didn't catch that.
- One more time.
My gosh.
(This is driving her crazy.)
Allow me to explain...
(Holding back her laughter)
Allow me to explain the next dish.
It's tteokbokki cooked...
using ghost pepper, which is the spiciest chili.
It has mala too, which makes it spicy...
and makes your tongue tingle.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(A decorous exit)
- I'll do the fritters.
- Okay.
(She can now cook the fritters at the same time.)
- Young Ji, as you do that, - Yes?
- shake this.
- I got it.
(Shake the broccoli!)
(On one side is basil.)
(On the other side are the fritters.)
(She has many things to manage.)
(Young Ji, the king of the kitchen, is in over her head.)
(She's suffering.)
Yes.
(In the empty space where mala used to be,)
Just this.
- Grind.
(basil pots have taken over.)
(Basil served)
(And Mimi's newest hardship)
Fine dining seems to be better in a way.
(Warm tteoksagna is ready.)
It's potato cream tteoksagna.
It's very hot.
Four of you will share one dish.
- Excuse me.
- We lose 5kg...
from making this.
We lose 5kg and then gain 5kg from tasting it.
(Oh, dear.)
Allow me to introduce you...
the final dish, potato cream tteoksagna.
It's lasagna made of potato cream and rice cake.
The pot is very hot, so please do not touch it.
You can divide it up and share.
- She's good at explaining, right?
- Yes.
She's coming up with that on the spot.
She's smart.
(Feeling bashful)
She's only 12.
(No!)
I'm not. I'm 24.
Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
I'll demonstrate first. Please copy me.
- Okay.
- Look here.
- It's like a kindergarten.
(It's like a kindergarten.)
- Here...
- Don't open it yet.
- Okay.
- Spread this open.
Torong...
- I'll copy you.
- I told you not to open it yet.
Sorry.
I knew they'd open it at least once.
Take Torong out gently.
Take it out gently.
Lay it on the plate...
- of your choosing.
- Okay.
You still need to watch.
- And...
- She's controlling.
- The teacher is so controlling.
Here's sugar powder.
I know you guys well,
so I have no choice but to become controlling.
Cover it...
and fold it in half like a mom.
- Amazing.
- Like this. Can you do it?
- I can do it.
- Can I open it?
- You can open it.
- Okay.
(Finally opening it to reveal Torong)
Here we go!
- I've always wanted to try this.
- I did this.
This is so fun.
(Lay Torong down 1 by 1.)
I think you can do that.
We can move the finished ones here.
It's easy when you put it down.
The blanket is...
I'll place it like this.
It's ramie.
His back must be very cold.
(I'm fine.)
Like steamed rice cake.
We get to try something like this.
We finished it.
(The plate is so clean that it looks like they washed it.)
- What luxury.
- I agree.
Hello.
Is the lasagna to your liking?
- Yes, it's delicious.
- It's delicious.
Do you mind if I slip in the dessert now?
- Yes, please.
- Of course.
It's the grand kick.
(Forks and knives for the dessert)
Don't you have too many things to wash?
It's okay.
Our arms have motors, so it's fine.
They must spend the whole day doing the dishes.
(She returns with the dishes.)
(Look at this empty pot.)
(They finished everything!)
(Empty pots make the owner happy.)
Dear customers, may I have your attention, please?
It's Torong...
What's the name?
Black sesame...
(Providing them with content until the very last moment)
Good Night Black Sesame Torong.
It's Good Night Black Sesame Torong Ice Cream.
I thought of the idea...
and decided to try it today.
Torong is sleeping.
We put a blanket made of sticky rice cake on him.
This is what I think.
When you love someone,
you want that person to sleep well.
That's what love is.
I hope you'll have a good night's sleep today.
- I love you.
(Look at this.)
- Here you go.
- Use a knife...
to cut sticky rice cake...
and have it with ice cream.
And the blanket with a hole...
is a ramie blanket. Summer edition.
(It's a summer-edition ramie blanket.)
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
This is our first and last fine dining.
We worked our butts off.
- It really wasn't easy.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for your hard work.
(We had a really good dinner thanks to you.)
It really wasn't easy,
but you enjoyed the food wholeheartedly,
which moved us deeply.
Once again, we'd like to thank you.
Allow us to express our gratitude.
We love you.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
(They're sad to see them go.)
We love you. Honesty, humility.
- Ahk.
(All the courses have been served.)
It was so funny.
Yu Jin was so funny.
(The customers enjoy the desserts too.)
It's so delicious.
(She stands up.)
- It's so good.
- It's so lucky to have this meal.
Gosh, my legs.
- Yes?
- No, not you.
Did you call?
- My bad.
- It's okay.
The toilet is behind the outdoor sink.
- I'll help you with the payment.
- Did you enjoy...
the meal?
Sixteen people.
That will be 320 dollars.
- We love you.
- Thank you.
- Please spread the word.
- Thank you. Go back safely.
(The customers leave Space Rice Cake's rice cake omakase.)
(Current time: 8:40pm)
The business...
(The 3rd day ends.)
is closed.
Goodbye.
Come again.
I love you.
Bye.
(Today's course is complete with the adorable sendoff.)
(Space Rice Cake's rice cake omakase ends.)
It was so fun.
Please give ourselves a round of applause.
That was an incredible job. Compliment yourselves.
(They put in all their efforts into the fine dining.)
You're the best.
We should really...
Honesty, humility.
- Ahk.
We're the best.
Boss, I want to rest.
Can I just tell you one thing?
- I want to go to Hawaii.
- Yes.
We'll be closed tomorrow.
- Is it our day off?
- Let's not do business...
- A day off.
- and just make rice cakes.
I'd rather...
Why?
- It sounds good.
- We won't do business tomorrow.
- My point...
is this.
We'll come to work at 12pm,
make rice cakes, and then go have fun.
- How does it sound?
- It sounds good, but...
(The boss' attempt to appease them doesn't encourage them much.)
What will you buy for us?
We really earned a lot today.
I'm thinking gimbap...
- Can we eat gimbap?
- Gimbap...
and rice cake.
We can have them.
- From ramyeon to that.
- From ramyeon...
(Deflated)
And lasagna.
So you're going downtown, right?
- Downtown, yes.
- Yes.
Our Teheran-ro.
We're going to the Teheran-ro of Goheung.
We're going downtown, which I've only heard rumors about.
Should I introduce you...
to the general store guy and the ingredients guy?
I desperately want a blind date.
- Then...
- When I was young,
my dream was to get married to a fried chicken shop owner.
- Then I'll arrange it...
- Tomorrow.
tomorrow.
Since we're going downtown,
- wear perfume and look pretty.
- Dress prettily.
- Is perfume enough?
- Dress up.
It's no joke.
Hold on. Tomorrow,
can we dress up similarly?
- Like how?
- The color.
What clothes did you bring?
- My clothes?
- Do you have white?
- I have white.
- White.
Do you have white?
(No.)
- White?
- I have white.
- White.
- Let's all dress in white.
- White...
- You don't have it.
I have it. This is the only white I have.
Wear Torong's T-shirt.
(Torong's T-shirt, got it.)
We'll dress in white tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Fully dress up, okay?
Fully dress up.
I have a wish as the head chef.
- Can you hear me out?
- Of course.
I'll say it only if you promise you'll do as I say.
- Then I won't do it.
- I'll see how it goes.
I'll see how it goes.
"I'll see how it goes."
- I learned from her.
- Tell me you'll definitely do it.
- I'll see how it goes.
I'll follow.
- Really?
- I mean,
- I'll follow the majority.
- What?
- I'll see how it goes.
- Let's hear it out.
- Go on.
- I want to take...
- the old-fashioned family portrait.
- Okay.
If we're doing that,
there's a face I want us to make...
- rather than a petty face.
- I'm serious.
Could it be the seal face?
- The seal face.
- Can I do that?
- Of course.
- Let's do it.
- Take the photo like this?
I like that. Mimi, can you try...
You got it.
- She got it.
- You got it.
That's it.
Do you know why? Because you're actually feeling empty.
That's your honest reaction.
- I want to do that.
- Shall we do a curtain call?
- Curtain call time.
- Today's curtain call.
On the count of three, say "yes."
- Then on the count of three...
- "Ang."
Shall we go with "ang?"
Say "ang" on the count of three. One, two, three.
- Ang.
- Honesty, humility.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
It's perfect. Please announce today's sales.
Today's sales.
(Today's sales are highly expected.)
It's 809.3 dollars.
It's 900 dollars.
- It's 809.3 dollars.
- So 900 dollars.
It's 800 dollars.
(9 original tteokbokki, 4 ghost pepper mala tteokbokki,)
(2 basil tteokbokki, 7 pollack roe and clam pasta, 8 cream tteoksagna,)
(9 Torong ice cream, 5 cream butter tteok,)
(21 slushy, 2 soft drinks)
(Rice cake omakase, 320 dollars, 20 dollars per person)
(Total sales: 809.3 dollars)
- Let's get off work.
- Let's go home.
- We'll rest tomorrow.
- Let's sleep in.
- We'll develop the menu tomorrow.
You're done. It's me.
This is our third day of business.
It's only the third day, but it feels like...
- It feels like the 28th day for me.
- Like the 28th day.
And a branch, at that.
It feels like I opened a branch after 28 days.
(A branch?)
(The fourth morning in Goheung)
(The sky is clear without any cloud,)
(and the sea is exceptionally blue.)
(Closed for business)
(Today is Space Rice Cake's day off.)
(What will the members do on their day off?)
Let's go get a massage.
- Sounds good.
- A foot massage, at least.
- Yes.
Get a full-body massage.
- Spend it all.
- We can earn back tomorrow.
Yes, we can earn back tomorrow.
These three women are incredible.
It's not easy to manage the kitchen.
I can leave the floor to Yu Jin and leave.
- You can't leave.
- No.
- I mean, Yu Jin...
- Where?
You were going to leave smoothly.
That was so smooth.
The kitchen can be managed perfectly without me.
- Eun Ji.
- Don't speak so elegantly...
- Exactly.
- when all you're saying is...
- You're going to run away today.
- you'll run away.
(Laughing)
Imagining it makes me salivate.
- Because you're happy?
- Imagining running away...
You're setting the stage to run away.
Imagining calling the manager...
and heading straight to Seoul? I imagined that all day yesterday.
No, I'll ride a KTX.
- Yeosu has a flight.
- I want to go to Yeosu.
Yeosu is great.
- Go to Yeosu and eat gatkimchi.
- And soy sauce marinated crabs.
(They dream of a Yeosu trip on their half-day off.)
We're closed.
We're closed for today.
- We're not open today.
- Let's eat.
(Current time: 12:30pm)
- Thank you for the food.
Eat tofu. It's protein.
Tofu.
Their boxed meal is good.
- It's good.
- It's so delicious.
The fried egg is over medium.
I love it.
It's perfect.
I'm so touched. It's over medium.
I don't need to think about cooking,
so I finished most of it.
You couldn't eat well...
- before you cooked?
- Yes.
Don't you agree? I just can't eat.
- Probably because you're nervous.
- Yes, because I'm nervous.
And it feels like my memory is declining here.
Why?
Like a habit, I keep saying,
"When I go back to Korea."
I keep calling Seoul Korea.
- "When I go back to Korea."
- You keep mentioning Seoul.
Because I want to go.
- You want to go to Seoul?
- Yes.
I'm scared now.
Every time Producer Ye Seul pays attention to what we say,
it comes true.
This is bad. I won't talk, then.
She's too scared to say anything.
Yu Jin, nice clothes.
That's become a habit for her.
Coffee slushy tastes even better.
- Yes.
- I like coffee slushy.
(Sweet coffee slushy after eating)
Here's your coffee slushy.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
(Teatime only possible on a day off)
You must have it cold.
(Happy)
It tastes like a latte sold in a cafe.
(It gets rid of their fatigue.)
- It's so tasty.
- It's so good.
- It's good.
- Producer, can I have a towel?
- For your head?
Yes, since I'm the king of the kitchen.
- Please write "gold" for Friday.
- "Gold," okay.
The head chef has a lot on her mind.
(She wears a bandanna and prepares to make rice cake.)
- The king progresses.
- The golden king.
- The king progresses...
I told them to treat me as a head chef,
and the king progresses...
(Deeply honored by the undeserved title)
We can't treat her well with our cooking skills,
so I'll treat her well with my attitude.
(The king will make rice cake.)
Get the latex gloves from the king.
- Not anyone can get one.
- Thank you.
It's gifted by the king.
- Thank you, King.
Thank you.
(Today's royal gift, latex gloves)
Your Highness, may I have the honor...
to wear the chin mask gifted by you?
- Here.
- Gosh, thank you!
Her Highness has gifted me the chin mask.
(Even when she turns on the steamer...)
Your Highness.
Her Highness is emptying the water.
(Let the music play!)
(She can't keep her dignity at the excessive flattery.)
Your Highness, what's next?
Opening the drain, and...
How dare you!
(The king becomes furious.)
I apologize.
- Heinous Lee Eun Ji!
- Yes.
- How dare you act so rudely!
- I am sorry.
The language of this country is different from that of China.
What...
I'm sorry.
- Yariyari yallaseong.
- Yalari yala.
- Heinous Lee Eun Ji.
- Yes.
- Move away right now.
- Yes, Your Highness.
(Scurrying)
Do not ever doubt me again.
"Do not ever doubt me again."
(The higher the throne, the lonelier its bearer.)
I never asked to treat me like a king.
Accept it. Being a king is your fate.
(She just wanted to be treated as the head chef.)
It's not "gold" for the golden king.
- It's "gold" for Friday.
- Being king is...
You're so annoying today.
(She chose the character without thinking much.)
(Everyone is mocking her.)
- Her Highness is washing her hands.
How...
What kind of king is this low of status?
A king is supposed to be under pressure...
from the right-hand man and the left-hand man.
That position as a king...
is a tough one when doing politics.
(The weight of the throne is too heavy.)
- We'll just make garaetteok today.
- Okay.
- Proceed with it.
What you always do.
Let's go.
(Measuring the soaked rice as usual)
- Mix it well.
- I got it.
(And mixing as usual)
Is everything going smoothly?
- Yes.
- You can do it.
(The kitchen is busy with rice cake-making.)
- Which one?
- Here it is.
You're so good at finding things.
Where did all the cameras disappear to?
I'm getting nervous.
Why aren't the cameras around?
What are they filming?
They must be filming remotely.
They're so skilled now.
Do it together.
(They start making garaetteok.)
- This is the best.
- You need to open a rice cake shop.
I got the hang of it.
This is perfect.
Eun Ji, this is absolutely perfect.
This is the best rice cake we've made so far.
- Yes.
- Yes, today is the best.
I want to live in Goheung.
- Really?
- Yes.
You want to stay here?
Yes, I want to stay here.
(For some reason, she wants to stay longer in Goheung today.)
- Then shall we get going?
- Let's go.
Let's go have fun.
(The excited members and dreary atmosphere)
- Shall we gather in the yard?
- Okay.
I'll just get changed.
Go out first.
(They get ready and gather in the yard.)
It's so cool.
Is that your downtown outfit?
Yes.
Yu Jin told us to wear white, so I did.
She's coming out.
- Can I go downtown like this?
- Sure.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'll go like this.
I am Queen Dowager
(And the last member)
You look pretty.
- You look like a first love.
- She's here.
- She has the first love look.
You look like a first love.
You must've waited for today to come.
So much. It's our Teheran-ro.
I even brought these shoes.
The downtown outfit.
Do we go to the photo studio first?
- The studio first?
- That's good and all,
but when you were making rice cakes,
the headquarters called.
What did they say?
They opened a second branch in Seoul.
What are you talking about? Now?
We're going to Seoul?
- We're going to Seoul?
- I told you.
- I finally got used to the kitchen.
- The kitchen and everything...
- We got used to this kitchen.
- Exactly.
I quit!
- Hold on.
- Go on a strike.
- Why?
- What's wrong?
- Young Ji...
- I can't do this.
- You wanted to go to Seoul.
This is different!
You said you wanted to go to Seoul.
- That's why they prepared this.
- No!
- I barely got used to the kitchen.
- If I say I want to do business...
in the USA, will we go there?
We were going to go there then.
If you'd said that, we would've done it.
- Is she dead?
- They need to adjust again...
- She...
- You want to go to the USA?
Young Ji, do you want to go to the USA?
Didn't you just say that you want to go to the USA?
She ran her mouth.
I love Seoul, though.
Hold on. We've finally gotten used to the whole system now.
We're starting to feel attached to the restaurant.
- I can't leave this place.
- No.
- Why...
- It's finally stabilized.
The HQ is saying...
since you've stabilized this place already,
come and do the same for the second branch...
with your expertise.
When you're in business, you have to expand.
(The second challenge they face)
(Yeonhui-dong, Seoul)
- Gosh, what?
- I'm intimidated.
- What?
- What is it?
(Shocked)
Hold on. This is a pop-up store.
- What is this? Get rid of it!
- What do we do now?
There are so many tables.
Seven, eight, nine...
- It's so new.
- We have new equipment.
- What is that?
- We're making burgers.
I think we have to make burgers.
Tomorrow, you'll hold a brand launch event.
I see. Like a pop-up store.
It's like a mini Met Gala.
Does this make sense?
It's obvious to see that we're doing it.
Gosh. This is quite the event.
A photowall?
Gosh. You look pretty, Chef.
Here is Mimi.
Eun Ji is here.
Goodness.
Please look to your left.
You look like Yang Hee Eun.
Look. This is the Met Gala now.
Congratulations.
(Laughing)
Louder!
Yes!
Thank you, everyone.
- One, two, three!
- Two, three!
(The grand opening...)
(of the 2nd branch of Space Rice Cake)
Bye, everyone.
Bye.
It's nice and cool.
For goodness' sake.
- What?
- Hello.
What is it? Am I forbidden to come here?
(Coming up next)
(We were selling tteokbokki in Goheung a moment ago.)
(I'm dreaming, right?)
(This has to be a dream.)
(This is real.)
(They're overwhelmed by the sheer scale of it.)
(So, Manager Kwon from the HQ comes to help them again!)
(Unveiling many new dishes...)
(that fit the vibe of Seoul!)
(This basil mayo is incredible.)
(This is more than just good.)
(It's so good that it makes you dance.)
(Totally satisfied with the new dishes)
(We're having burgers for the staff meal today.)
(Delivery versus Space Rice Cake, Burger showdown)
(Are we even getting mock reviews?)
(Do we get brutally honest reviews right after practicing it?)
(Chop the onions.)
(How are we going to do all this within an hour?)
(The race against the clock begins amid the tension.)
(We just learned the recipe today.)
(We learned it today.)
(As the time limit approaches,)
(their hands move faster.)
(And the staff starts to gather.)
(The final evaluation of the staff meal)
(Maybe it's a harsh review.)
(What now?)
(What will become of the new dishes...)
(prior to the grand opening of the 2nd branch?)
(Space Rice Cake)